http://www.bagsunlimited.com/topic/privacy

Login
View Cart (0)
View Wishlist (0)
Shipping
Privacy Statement for Bags Unlimited Inc.
Bags Unlimited Inc. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy.  The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: www.bagsunlimited.com  and www.bagssuperstore.com
Information Automatically Logged
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site.  Your IP address is also used to help identify you and your shopping cart.
Cookies
Our Site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart.
Collection and Use of Personal Information
The information we may ask you to input includes your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card information, shipping information, and a password.  We collect some or all of this information when you purchase items through our electronic commerce offerings or if you register to choose to participate in other interactive offerings on our website.  We may use the personal information you provide to process purchases of Bags Unlimited Inc. merchandise, to deliver products and prizes to you, and to communicate with you directly.  We may also send e-mails to you regarding promotions, newsletters, new offerings, or features.
We do not provide any personally identifiable information to third parties not affiliated with Bags Unlimited Inc.
Not Sharing Personal Information
Please know that any personal information that you provide to us is voluntary on your part and not required by Bags Unlimited Inc.
Security
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.
Contacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:
webmaster@bagsunlimited.com
Home    About Us    Contact Us    Customer Service    Security    Privacy Policy
View wishlist
Shopping Cart:
0
Items
Your shopping cart is currently empty.
Please select an item and add it to your cart.
Discounts:
Total:
$0.00
Close
Checkout
View cart
Your Wishlist:
0
Items
Your wish list is currently empty. Please select an item and add it to your wishlist.
Total:
$0.00
Close
Move all to Cart
Loading...
